Welcome to episode 10.5 of Under the
Hood. Why 10.5 you might ask? Well,
actually we have already recorded
episode 11. Uh and you should actually
look forward to it. We are going to talk
about summary and how we do um summary
with AI. Uh but before uh before that uh
we wanted to address the whole vibe
coding thing. There's so much people
talking about vibe coding these days. Um
then we wanted to do something about it.
So this is kind of a special edition of
under the hood and today with me I have
Stefan. Hi Stefan.
>> Hi.
>> So Stefan, let's let's dive right into
it. What is VIP coding? You know people
might have heard about it. Um and so
tell us a little bit what what what is
it?
>> Yeah. So basically it's just uh using AI
to help you code, right? So help you get
started with your coding and get get
things going. So you can think of it as
a as like a colleague you want to have
code some work for you or somebody who's
sitting right next to you. You just want
to chat with them and get them to to
build some code for you.
>> So So we have had uh AI in GitHub with
GitHub copilot in VS Code for for a
while when you had like suggestions for
completions and things like that.
Exactly. So how how but that's not the
same. It's a little bit different,
right? Exactly. Coding is like, you
know,
>> yeah, we're taking it one step further
using the agent mode in in VS code here
or in other tools and we are letting the
agent itself build and reason over some
data and figure out how to build the
actual code it wants to build. So we are
not telling it exactly what we want to
build, but we're kind of giving it the
framework, the context of what we want
to build. And that's what we're going to
try now.
>> Okay. So that's Yeah.
Show us like a minimalact hello world
vibe coding thing.
>> Exactly. So, so here I just have a
project this empty project just from
algo and and I want to build something
here and I'm just going to tell it here
I want to build let's say add a shoe
size to the customer field right. So
>> I want to add a page extension
with shoe size
oh size and we want a backing field for
that. So, we're going to add a table
extension
to the customer table
uh with shoe size.
>> So, you're just you're not even writing
code. You're just telling
>> exactly
>> to the agent what uh what you want.
>> Exactly. Like like a colleague next
door. I would say to him,
>> by the way, is there something special
you need to do in VS Code to be able to
do that?
>> Well, so here I just have the the GitHub
copilot chat window, right? And I set
the agent mode down here.
>> You need to meet in agent mode.
>> Exactly. you receive the ask and the
edit and now there's also the agent mode
>> and I like the GT5 preview right now uh
because that's one of the newest models
you can choose from a lot of other
models uh and you have to figure out
which one that works for you
>> uh I've had good success with this one
so I'm going to use this one
>> and then just execute and see what
happens agent here will go and figure
out what to do and we'll just be waiting
here and we see that it's actually using
a reference
in this case he's looking for some code
generation instructions from GitHub
copilot and now it's reading the app
JSON to figure out the ID range for the
object similar to what I would do if I
had to create something.
>> So you kind of kind of follow along
what's going on, what the agent is
doing.
>> Exactly. And we can see it's now
creating some files. Something's going
on here. It's created a table extension
and it creates a page extension and it's
just keep working there until it's kind
of done with what we asked it to do.
Mhm.
>> And it's looking for a lot of other
things here. We can actually follow
along with the code here. So, we can
actually minimize this window here and
just view the data. So, we can see it's
added a table extension that extends the
customer table and it added the shoe
size field. And we can see here that
here we have the page extension that
added the shoe size field. And it even
added a tool tip. I didn't ask for that,
>> but it kind of reasoned that would be a
good idea to have a tool tip here.
>> And that seems like a good idea. So,
we'll just keep that. And here we can
now see where it is at. Um,
it tells me what it did. So, it added
the two files, the table extension and
the page extension. And then it actually
suggests me to do next.
>> Oh, you get a small summary of what
happened.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah.
>> And suggest what you could do.
>> Exactly.
>> Okay. Pretty cool. So, so just to so
there's a lot of vibe coding out there,
you know, there tons of videos and and
and tutorials and stuff. uh but not too
many about AL. Uh but actually vibe
coding also works as you just show for
for for AL. It's not I mean the agents
and models are are pretty good with AL
too, right?
>> I I think so. Yeah, it's actually doing
a pretty good job here. There's really
nothing that that doesn't work in what
it's created here. Uh so this would
compile if I click the build and it will
actually create an extension for me.
>> So I noticed something for example that
it it uh it figures out which ID to use.
>> Exactly. Yeah, somehow it fig,00
so it has some it has some uh insight
into the project and it's probably
looking into the uh maybe the appj
it did actually. We can see up here that
it actually looked at the app.
>> Okay, that's probably where it got that.
>> So it knows a lot of things about
building extensions for business
central. It knows that we use ids and it
knows that it has to go to the app JSON
file to find the range that it can use
because that's all documented out there.
>> Pretty cool.
>> So the model has learned all of that.
>> But in order for us to like really get
something out of it, we need to continue
building on this.
>> So let's just add validation on it,
right? Let's just say that.
>> Yeah.
>> Add validation that checks the shoe size
is between
what? 15 and 62
>> for example. Yeah,
>> 62. Yeah,
>> that's big feet. But
>> I guess that depends on which kind of
metrics you're using.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Again, we see what it's doing.
It's reading some some data from the
context of the project here. And it
knows that in Business Central, we have
something called an unvalidate trigger.
>> Okay.
>> And now it's actually going to implement
that for us. And we can go to the table
extension and we can actually see it
implementing
the validation here and erroring out if
>> it doesn't work. If
>> it's wrong
>> and every time you can choose whether
you keep the the changes or and
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah. So this this version of of an
agent has these checkpoints that you can
go back to. So you can restore a
checkpoint if you feel that it went off
track.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay. you can go back to uh like the
previous stage you were in
>> exactly and at any time you can say okay
now we're kind of done with this so I'll
keep all of that and we can check that
in I'm going to submit that
>> okay
>> but in order for us to do real vibe
coding
>> we need to step away from the code
>> to take ourselves away from the actual
implementation details
>> but you need to look at the code anyway
a little bit
>> yeah yeah so that that's where the
developer has a hard challenge right to
step away from the code and actually
look at at giving the agent space to
implement something and just iterate on
the actual definition of the project you
want to implement rather than than
looking at the specific validation code
here. Right?
>> And that's the next big thing.
>> Okay. So this is this is a um this is
cool. This is like a hello world
example. It uh but how you know what's
your experience because people might
argue okay it's it's a simple extension.
It's not a real world example. So what's
your experience with you know bigger
bigger project like let's say uh you
know as a partner developer you have
maybe this larger solution which is
based on top of uh which is extending
business central uh can you vibe code uh
in that environment as well and what
does that work
>> so so I I think there's a there's a
couple of different ways you can use
this tool as we do here we we implement
something simple and we do prototyping
and all these things but if you want to
implement something that is in a a
context. You need to narrow down the
context. You need to figure out what
exactly is it the agent can help you
with. And one of the things that the
agent is really good at is all the
scaffolding, all the creations like it
create a new table. Okay, it can do
that.
>> But actually going in and manipulating
small details that are in your existing
application that maybe has a lot of
years on it or complex design, that's
going to be a little bit difficult for
the agent.
>> So you have to figure out which parts of
your application it can help you. Mhm.
>> Uh this could be like creating a
permission set. It will find all the the
tables that you need and it will create
the permission set.
>> Yeah. That's that's you know
traditionally it's a little bit tedious.
>> Exactly. Exactly. Create a page or list
page or the cart page and it will
actually figure out which fields belong
together. Reason over the data that's
there.
>> A lot of the boilerplate code can can be
you know written by the agent quite
quickly.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely.
Absolutely. So it can actually be quite
fast to use these tools
>> if you find the right scenarios. So you
talked about context.
>> Yes.
>> So tell us a little more about it.
Agents usually are performing better if
they have a better context for. So
what's you know what's the what's the
approach when you're vaping? How do you
provide context to uh to the agent?
>> So you have the opportunity to uh to
define the the context it needs to work
on by specifying certain uh symbols. For
example, if in this case I wanted it to
only work on my table,
>> I could put in the table as a as a
syntax syntax here. So say customer
table like this one.
>> Okay.
>> Say this is the symbol I want to work
on. So I can give it a little more
information on this one.
>> So the hashtag file, what does that do?
>> That's the symbol to point to a symbol
in your project. Right?
>> I can also add files in my project if I
wanted to know about some files. I can
add some documentation.
>> Mhm. I can
>> So you could have a readme file for
example.
>> Read me file.
>> Markdown in markdown.
>> Exactly.
>> Format or something like that.
>> So the more context you give to the to
the project to the agent in that it's
able to read specs readme doc comments
all these things will give it more
information to work with and reason
over.
>> So if it knows the the purpose of the
function then it will also be uh able to
make a decision whether to use a
function. the same with the page and the
table and so forth.
>> So would you recommend that when you
start vibe coding for a serious project
you maybe write down what you know what
kind of a small specification of some
kind to help the agent?
>> I think that that's an excellent idea
and I think that's where you get to the
true vibe coding where you don't need to
look at the actual code. You talk about
the spec. You talk about what is it that
you want to achieve
>> by implementing this
>> and then when you have a spec you can
tell the agent go implement it.
>> Got it. just go and get it done, right?
>> We can try. I have actually a
>> a small prompt that I created
>> and I'm just going to paste it in here
because it's a little bigger than what
we did before.
>> Mhm. So, you've prepared this in
advance, but it's basically just it's
basically just uh text, right?
>> Exactly. Exactly. Let's see. There we
go. So, here I have the prompt that I
created
>> and I'm just going to scroll to the top
here.
So the prompt is that the agent is
acting as a collaborator developer my
peer here. I'm actually
>> always a good idea to define the role
>> exactly scope it down to what we're
trying to do here and we want to build a
business central extension
>> for managing properties rentals and
service requests.
>> So we can think of this as a complete
vertical in business central like
something a big project that we're going
to start.
>> Um and before we want to start coding we
want to make sure that when we think
about the coding we want to think about
the functional requirements first.
>> Mhm. like we would do with a colleague
talk about what are we implementing, how
are we supposed to do it and then we
want to uh make sure that when we write
ale code we follow some guidelines and
here we have the the link to the
communitydriven vibe coding guidelines.
>> Okay.
>> So I've used that as a as instructions.
>> So the agent will go and and look that
up.
>> Exactly. So that means that it will
actually take some of these instructions
here and use them when they actually
generate code.
>> Correct.
>> And then I'm just going to say well
let's start with 10 questions.
>> Mhm. Let's start with 10 important
questions about what we're building so
we can actually get started without
starting with the code. We want to start
with the spec instead.
>> Okay.
>> This is where I don't need to know how
it implements this,
>> but I need to make sure it follows my
spec.
>> Right.
>> So, you're asking the agent actually to
ask questions.
>> Exactly. Yeah. Clarify and in that also
reason over what we have done and what
we will do. Let's try it out. See what
happens.
>> So, it's going to work a little bit
because this is a bigger prompt. It's
going to take a little
>> by the way a good trick uh also
something I don't know if you if you've
done that but when you write a prompt
like this what you can do uh with
benefit is to get that prompt that you
wrote and and uh put it through say GPT
or copilot and ask copilot or some some
AI to actually improve that prompt.
>> Exactly. Uh so you you write it the best
you can but usually um you know getting
it through this first refinement stage
you know can provide really really good
results uh because models are also
trained to do that kind of thing and
they know how to to write you know a
better prompt on themselves.
>> Exactly. Exactly. And and my prompt here
was super simple.
>> I didn't write any context on it. Like
normally you would build build something
that's a little more detailed about what
you want to build. But even with this
>> even with this simple prompt and you see
here it's it's it got me a whole lot of
questions, whole lot of recommendations.
>> And if we go through some of these we'll
find that it actually put in some stuff
that is business central specific.
>> Okay.
>> So it combined my prompt with the
knowledge of
>> you give an example.
>> Well, we have some here around uh
building a custom tenant table. So for
the the people who are renting a
property here
>> or link it or and link it here to the
customer table which is part of business
central core product right so it knows
about that
>> if I had my own solution next to it I
could bring bring in that context and
say I have these tables figure out how
you can use them right
>> I have this data I have this
functionality figure out how you can use
that in this solution also
>> pretty cool
>> but because it's business central it can
find it in the existing training so we
can go through this and we can see that
there's lots of good questions
questions, things that we might want to
think about when we build projects like
this.
>> And
>> so that's kind of also kind of a help to
actually write a better specification
and provide even better context to
>> Exactly. Exactly. And if we save these
in a file, the the questions and answers
here, we'll be able to go back to it
later.
>> Mhm.
>> But let's continue with this one. Let's
see.
>> Yeah.
>> What it's going to do here. It's just
going to I'm going to take the easy way
out, right?
We don't have time for going through
this, but I do recommend that people
take time,
>> answer the question the best they can so
that we get the best solution possible.
For now, I'm just going to
>> Yeah, for the purpose of this demo,
we'll just go over here. But but yeah,
you could potentially review all these
and and and kind of, you know, adjust it
and fine tune it.
>> Be curious about some of the the other
things that the agent can do, right? So,
I'm just going to accept all here
>> and see what happens.
>> Now, it starts actually writing some
code.
>> No, not yet.
>> Not yet. Okay.
>> Well, I I don't expect it to. Okay.
Okay.
>> Right. So now it's made a checklist of
all that needs to be done here.
>> Okay.
>> It's then done a specification for
version 0.2.
>> Mhm.
>> And it tells me that it's going to
create the or at least have a spec for
some tables. I mean we have here
multiple tables just from the words I
put in from the beginning like the the
properties leases and
>> so is the uh the assignment is to create
a uh
>> a spec first, right?
>> A spec. But that's what's the uh what's
the do we start creating rental
management?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Property management, right?
It's
>> just a sample.
>> So the real it's a real scenario.
>> It's a real scenario. Yeah. Some
something that is a vertical that
doesn't integrate deep into business
central but actually stands next to it.
Okay.
>> If you want to integrate deep into
business central, you need to provide
more context about where in business
central you want to integrate into. So
for this demo, I put something that is
>> semiconnected but not fully integrated.
Right? So we still have it still hasn't
produced any code at that stage. It's
still we're still working on the
basically specifying the work more or
less. Right.
>> Exactly. And even here I told it to ask
me 10 questions.
>> But even after these 10 question and the
answers I gave accept all.
>> It's it's going to ask me more questions
because it reasoned that there is going
to be more work to be done. We need to
understand something more before we even
go go on with this. So I'm just going to
skip this and just say let's implement
it. So
>> now we areing code.
>> Well, I'm not writing any code.
>> No, but okay. The agent does. All right.
>> Is is actually writing the code. So
let's see if the it actually can can be
implemented. Again, we specified that it
should use the AL guidelines on the the
the communitydriven VIP coding site.
>> And
>> so you'll get with that you'll get the
the uh the coding styles from the
>> I'm hoping Yeah, we'll get that. Again,
if you look at at a peer, you're talking
to a peer and you tell him to use these
style guides, he will most likely use
them, but there's no guarantee.
>> That's that's a fair fair comparison.
That's a good way to look at it, I
guess.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> Exactly. But what I can do with whatever
it produces here, we can see it's
already producing some tables, pages,
and code units, and so forth.
>> I could just press F5 and see if it
builds and then go to the browser and
check out the product that I've built.
>> Yeah. And then I could say, okay, well,
I don't like these fields and can vibe
code some more.
>> I don't need to look at the code.
>> For true VIP coding, you need to detach
yourself from the code.
>> Okay,
>> I can also go directly into
>> I couldn't help notice also when you as
you set up on the screen, you have uh
you know the agent window is is way
bigger than uh than the actual code
window. You can barely actually read the
code in in that's a totally different
way to approach coding, right?
Absolutely.
>> Absolutely. Um,
>> I'm I'm not going to overstate it is
it's just because I work this way. There
are going to be situations where I need
to go into the code and understand what
the challenge is, right? Because it's
not magic here, right?
>> Almost. It feels a little bit like
magic, right?
>> I mean,
>> so there's also this um, as you
mentioned before, there's also this, you
know, vibe coding is also um, there's
this iterative aspect of it, right? And
and maybe the reason why it has been so
popular and people are you know so
excited about it is because as opposed
to maybe just asking some AI write some
code as a one-off thing the vibe coding
uh process is much more iterative you
know you you uh you you start with some
code and then you you get some some the
agent to write something and then you
you ask you know the agent add a field
or you know fix that algorithm and then
you you do another iteration and And and
when you think about it that resembled a
lot the way you know traditional coding
works. You know coding is much is very
much like that. you know, you start
writing something simple, you know,
write a few line of code, try it out,
you know, add, you know, add some more
things, add some test, you know, add an
extra functionality and and then you try
it out as you go. Uh, and I think the
reason why maybe it's so, you know,
there's so much hype about it and people
are so excited about it because it's
it's so close to uh what, you know, what
programmers do all the time. Uh, and it
feels very natural. Uh and it feels you
know it's like having somebody to help
you with the tedious stuff and you
exactly that's that's what it's so I
think it's so uh it's so great because
you know we we all we all tried it if
you code you know they they yeah
permissions or you know we start with a
new page you have a lot of you know
define the field and all that it's not
it's not really the interesting part but
you have to do it and that's where
agents and and AI is great because it
can you know get you you know through
these things very very quickly and then
can spend time on the, you know, the
more, you know, interesting things and
maybe the harder the harder part of the
code that needs more, you know, more
attention, right?
>> Exactly. Exactly.
>> It's still working.
>> Yeah, it's still And it can continue to
work for some time. So, you might think,
well, couldn't I code this faster
myself? And yeah, some people can. They
have fast fingers, but but is that what
you want to spend your time on?
>> Or do you want to spend the time on
thinking about what's the next steps?
What are the things that we're missing?
What are the
>> the things that we need to do next here?
Right. That that's maybe more
interesting as you say what's the
algorith I think you know how many how
it's been working like for what like 1
minute or so one and a half minutes
already created I can see five or six
>> well
>> objects or something like that even more
created
>> I think you need to be really fast if
you
>> pages yeah a lot of pages lots of
permissions tables
>> or you need to be quite fast if you if
you want to create this in the same
amount of time I don't think I can
>> no no so so if you look at it isolated
one file one thing. Yes, maybe you could
do it. But
>> but building all of this and having it
be connected from the beginning like it
knows the table relationships, it knows
what the pages needs to have, what
source tables and what fields and so
forth.
>> All of this is a great offset. Like you
get started really fast with this
>> and you don't really need to do much
more than just ask it.
>> So there's a lot of uh people saying,
you know, I've seen a lot of people uh
saying, "Yeah, I've tried VIP coding."
And then you you start v coding is all
great and then you you you spend you
know 10 minutes uh generating code and
two hours debugging you afterwards. I
see a lot of people saying that. So
what's your experience? Is that is that
true? Is that a lot of you know it looks
great? You know it demos really well
>> uh but how much is the code actually you
know production quality afterwards and
and how much you know time spend
debugging it?
>> Yeah. Um
>> so so when we first started with the
with agent mode and we had the maybe the
GT4 and all these things it was not as
good as it is today. GT5 claw models the
newer ones and other newer models are
much better at AL. So it will actually
generate building code because I'm using
it inside VS Code. You will also see
sometimes in in the the process that it
will actually look at the symbols that
we're processing in the background and
it will look at the the compilation
results and diagnostics that we
processing. So it will actually
>> change course every now and then figure
out oh that was wrong I need to go back
and fix that error or fix that
diagnostic.
>> Yeah so as you mentioned before it has a
lot more context than if you just go to
chatgpt or copilot and and and ask it to
write code there. it doesn't have uh
feedback the feedback I mean here it
actually tried to compile the the
whatever code you're writing and and see
the errors the warnings you know I've
seen it for even the warnings if you get
warnings in you when you build it goes
and okay try to fix the warning and then
goes goes again and try again and so all
these context you are having in it's
much more than just having uh you know
writing code through GPT or other just
chat interface this is really integrated
with the whole
>> interactive essentially Yeah, exactly.
>> And and we can just try whatever it's
finished building here, it's there's an
error, right? So sometimes it doesn't
fix all of them and we need to go look
at it
>> and that happens because
>> uh it doesn't always get the signals at
the right time. So then you need to feed
it back. You can just copy the error
message, put them back into the the the
chat and
>> so it finishes there, but there's an
error.
>> Yeah. So we see there's lots of lots of
issues here. So we can go fix that. We
can just copy the the problems here. Let
me take the output here.
>> Just take a few.
>> Okay.
and copy them and just say, well,
>> fix that.
>> I'm not going to do that.
>> You just paste the error. You don't even
ask. So, you kind of understand that's
what you want.
>> Fix.
>> Well, it reasons that the reason why I'm
putting this in is because uh
>> yeah, it's going to fix some issues.
>> All right, here we go.
>> So, even if it didn't pick it up, in
this case, it didn't for some reason. Uh
>> I don't know why, but sometimes it it it
doesn't pick up all the errors, all the
issues, and then you just feed them back
in. And
>> so is that because it's it gets a better
it do it does a better job working like
one error at a time afterwards than when
you have the whole when you try to
handle the whole
>> B. So right now there is no compile
method for the the agent to call.
>> Okay.
>> Uh so it relies on the diagnostics to be
produced while it's building
>> and when it's done and we didn't get the
diagnostics then it's just going to see
the errors right at the end. So we need
to feed them back in.
>> Okay. And maybe there's some issues
around generating. So maybe it cannot
>> make the decision. So like here it's
going to ask me something. I'm just
going to run a full compile.
There we go. And now it worked.
>> All right.
>> Like that's all I have to do now. It
just worked.
>> Okay. Talking about which uh Stefan you
are you are, you know, the lead of the u
uh compiler team. Yeah.
>> Uh so is there anything you're working
on right now uh we are doing to uh to
help uh this experience in the future?
Are we going to introduce some new
things in the compiler, new features in
the whole the AL development experience?
So, so the agent experience is going to
be better. Tell us a little bit about
it.
>> Yeah. So, I just talked about the
compile.
>> Yeah.
>> And that's part of the whole we need to
give the agent more tools,
>> right?
>> So, compile is one of them. We also are
thinking maybe we should add the ability
to publish it and we're looking into
test execution.
>> Okay? Because if the if the agent is
able to not only build the code but also
force a compilation and also write
tests,
>> publish extensions and then execute the
test and get feedback.
>> Then it can do the whole loop itself.
>> That would be really cool.
>> That could be kind of cool.
>> So are we working on that?
>> We are actually working on that right
now. So that's in the scope right now.
>> But I just want to return to something
we said in the in the beginning here.
Context is key here, right? So one of
the things you'll find when you're
working with the business central is
it's not all symbols that it can find.
>> Okay.
>> So what we are working alo on also is
adding MCP servers. So the model context
protocol
>> for giving the agents more context to
work with.
>> And
>> so if you if you haven't heard about MCP
just you know briefly MCB stand for
model context protocol. It's basically a
standard um it's an open source standard
right uh and it's um it's it's mostly a
discovery mechanism that allows agents
to uh so agents are trained now to uh
understand and and know about MCP
>> and uh by exposing some capabilities as
an MCP server you can uh you know
there's some discovery mechanism and and
uh and agents and and AI can do
intelligent thinks about about this. So
think of it as a um you know a way to
expose what kind of tools you have. Is
that is that fair to say that's what it
is? Absolutely. So you have a in our
there's tons of MCP servers out there if
you you know if you haven't heard look
it up. There's a lot we have actually an
MCP server for documentation.
>> Exactly.
>> Which you can can you maybe you can show
how you add an MCP server to uh to your
context when you are in VS Code.
>> Yeah. So I actually I actually have it
in the MCP server here. So you can see
here these are the the tools that are on
here. That's the tools for this agent.
>> And I am actually using the MSAN. So the
docs MCP server.
>> Yes,
>> you can discover uh more MCP servers
from your extensions. So you can go down
here to MCP servers. Let me make this a
little bit bigger. So below the
extensions there is MCP servers
installed. I have actually the doc
twice. So this uh this actually gives VS
code VS code agent access to our
documentation the BC documentation and
it has an API and through this MCP
protocol what it does basically say ah
okay there's an API I can call
>> and I can ask you know search on the
documentation and that that when it uh
it writes some code or or respond to
your your request it actually look look
into
>> so use these exactly and you can find
even more here like you click the button
here there's many other and there are
some extensions that also produce um MCP
servers like the context 7 one I have
here
>> and we are thinking about adding even
more like the one we have for business
central is more about getting access to
the customer data
>> right
>> but we need to add an MCP server that
gives you access to the the environment
metadata so that will give you uh what
symbols exist on the server
>> and then we want to broaden that out so
you can actually develop even more with
this metadata MCP server.
>> So that will mean that the old hype
coding experience would be probably even
more powerful and can do more things and
less maybe less errors and and more
advanced.
>> Exactly. Yeah. So of course errors and
other diagnostics we need to look at
those how can we communicate to the
agent what needs to change
>> what can we do better in order to help
it guide itself to the next solution.
>> All right.
>> Right. Yeah.
>> So lots of good stuff here. You can also
add your own if just to take that also.
So if you go to uh the functions you can
just add your own MCP server if you have
one on your own company.
>> Okay.
>> Your own docs. Uh maybe you have your
own development resources.
>> So you could expose that to an MCP
server and edit it. So you have that
context as well.
>> Exactly.
>> Cool. And if you go up here again as a
as an alternative of providing context
to MCP and to the files, we had the this
the coding guidelines from the web from
the community. But you can also add your
own just by going to uh the chat
configuration and look at your
instructions, prompt files and so forth,
right? So you can go there and actually
add your own instructions. So when you
create a table, it must have this prefix
or whatever you want to have.
>> Okay. So you Yeah. So you can basically
add some um it it's going is going to
end up in the prompt eventually right
instruction that will be added to every
prompt uh and it could be for example
guidelines or anything you think you
know always indent like this or whatever
you
>> rules you have at your company right so
whatever is is required for making the
code the best quality
>> always name procedure according to that
uh that scheme or whatever
>> always document public methods and all
that Okay. Yeah, that's a that's a good
one, too. Yeah.
>> So, lots of things you can do with this.
Yeah.
>> Okay. So, uh that that's super great.
So, how um if we um if if partners and
developers want to get started with vibe
coding, what what's your what's your
recommendation? How you know how should
they go about it?
>> Yeah.
>> Uh first of all, is that something Yeah.
Let me ask before that. Is that
something that uh you you would
recommend people use also for production
uh production grade coding?
>> Yes. Yeah, absolutely. I mean,
>> so it's not just a toy. It's
>> No, no, it's it's almost never too late
to start, right? And you have to start.
You have to try it out. You have to
figure out what you can use it for. This
is a productivity tool.
>> It will help you do all the tedious, the
scaffolding, all the the things that you
have to do again and again and again
easy. And it's going to be so much
>> um of a benefit to you as an individual
developer because you can be much more
productive and focus on the right
things.
>> But it's also going to give you a better
connection to maybe
customers or consultants to allow them
to describe things and help translate
that into code.
>> It doesn't need to be onetoone, but it
will help you translate it into code. So
just go get started, figure out what you
can use it for, try it out, and every
new model that comes out will be even
better than the one.
>> That's we can pretty much predict that.
>> We can pretty much that's what we have
seen at least that's been the trend so
far. There's so much difference between
even the four models and and the four
models and and GP5 and and I hear also
that the clothes on it is very good at
people are also giving good feedback on
this but uh
>> different tools you should try you
should try which one actually works for
you there's a bit of a of you know a
taste people like better GPT5 people
like better code this you know just try
it out there these models are available
there are several of them available in V
code
>> and don't stick to one model. Don't say
it's only that model. Try different
models. So when you feel like you're
getting stuck with one model for one
scenario, go try something else like
experiment a little with the models
>> and you can change model at any time.
>> Exactly. Or just go down here in this
case here. Just go down, pick another
model, then continue the chat
>> and then yeah, you get a new result, a
different way of reasoning.
>> All right. So last question uh before we
u conclude that's that was really cool.
uh it's a little bit scary still right I
mean how much you know how much do you
think this is going to uh you know what
does it mean for whole developer
community right
>> um it's a little bit scary you know
people think I'm sure there are people
thinking out there is it going to
replace my job
>> so what's your what's your thinking on
that
>> yeah so so I think I think um for me
personally it's a productivity tool so
it helps me build the things faster or
at least get me started faster all the
scaffolding as we talked about
>> but it's also a way for me to get inspir
operation
uh because it will it will help me
expand my knowledge like uh maybe I
don't know enough about number series I
can ask it about numbers here how to
integrate so that's like from a personal
point of view it's a productivity tool
obviously uh if if you're just working
on creating permission sets
>> this might replace that but I think we
as developers are
>> are prone to problem solving and we'll
find the solutions using these tools in
a more efficient way
>> so I don't think my job is going away
tomorrow. That's not what I'm saying.
>> I I think I think it's fair to say that
there's a lot of work out there and
usually it's more, you know, that's what
we hear from, you know, a partner
channel, but that's also true for
ourselves. You know, we have so many
things in our backlog uh and and we we
we can never, you know, get everything
done in in in one release. So, so with
these tools, you know, our expectation
is that we will actually be able to be
more productive and get more features
out, you know, and uh and because the
expectation is still there, there's
still a lot of things to do. And I think
that goes for, you know, uh any
industry, any solution out there build
on BC. Uh people are usually, what we
hear is that people have, you know, a
lot of demands, a lot of customers, and
they have a hard time to keep up with
with the requests from the, you know,
from their customers. So we, you know,
that could be a way to actually get more
done and be more efficient and u and you
know have a better a better YP
experience and a better product.
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah, totally agree.
>> All right, say thank you very much. That
was that was really great. And um yeah,
if you um if you have some comments and
if you want to, you know, know more
about what we are going to do with W
coding, put some uh put some question in
um in the comments below. And uh thank
you for watching.